Guide to the American political campaigns miscellany, 1868-2016
American political campaigns miscellany
- Series IX. Paper Miscellaneous
  - "Assemblywoman Barbara Lifton fought for a bipartisan budget...,", 2007; 6477.PM0142; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - "Health Care. It's not a luxury...,", 2007; 6477.PM0143; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - "This little guy wants you to ...", 2007; 6477.PM0144; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Meier, Ray
    Party: Right-to-Life
  - Washington Times Souvenir [Inauguration] edition, 1/21/1985, 1985; 6477.PM0145; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - Ronald Reagan photograph, dedication of Presidential Library, 1991; 6477.PM0146; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - Capitol Insights, News and Views, 2003; 6477.PM0147; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Seward, James L.
  - "News from Senator James L. Seward,", 200-; 6477.PM0148; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - "Senator Seward - cutting taxes on families,", 2007; 6477.PM0149; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - "It was never really about who Eliot Spitzer was standing up to,", 2006; 6477.PM0150; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Spitzer, Eliot
  - "Change the World,", 2006; 6477.PM0151; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - "Vote Eliot Spitzer for Governor,", 2006; 6477.PM0152; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - The Suozzi Story, 2006; 6477.PM0153; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Suozzi, Thomas
  - "It's been 8 years... ...Had enough?, 2006; 6477.PM0154; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - "You too can be the life of the party," Howard Whitman, Woman's Home Companion, 8/1952 [pp. 44, 121-124], 1952; 6477.PM0155; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - American Political Items Collectors catalogue, 2005; 6477.PM0156; Items: 3 (Box 27)
  - "Let's Elect Jack Alexander", 6477.PM0157; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Alexander, Jack
  - "You are there...with Ted Black", 6477.PM0158; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Black, Ted
  - "Elect the Responsible Republican--Dick Bond", 6477.PM0159; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Bond, Dick
  - "It's time for a change. Elect James Chew", 6477.PM0160; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Chew, James
  - "Standing up for New York", 6477.PM0161; Items: 2 (Box 28)
  - "Ten Reasons to Re-Elect Clinton/Gore", November, 1996; 6477.PM0162; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Clinton, Bill and Al Gore
  - "Collins for Congress" pamphlet and newspaper, November 3, 1968; 6477.PM0163; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Collins, Jim
  - Fred Compagni campaign mailer, 6477.PM0164; Items: 4 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Compagni, Fred
  - "Vote for Jodie Connell" pamphlets, 6477.PM0165; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Connell, Jodie
  - "Mayoral Candidates take their Final Jabs" Ithaca Journal newspaper, October 31, 1989; 6477.PM0166; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Cookingham, Jean and Benjamin Nichols
  - "Cortum for Congress", 6477.PM0167; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Cortum
  - "Vote for Curtis C. Crawford", 6477.PM0168; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Crawford, Curtis
  - "Senator Al D'Amato wants your Opinion", 1982; 6477.PM0169; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: D'Amato, Al
  - "Dave Crowley for Congress" mailer, August 17, 1982; 6477.PM0170; Items: 4 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Crowley, Dave
  - "Nominate a Republican Winner for Congress in the New Third District", 6477.PM0171; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Curtis, Laurence
  - "Elect George Dentes", 2000; 6477.PM0172; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Dentes, George
  - Esther Dotson newsletter, pamphlet, 1966; 6477.PM0173; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Dotson, Esther
  - "John Dyson Speaks Out", 6477.PM0174; Items: 1 (Box 28)
  - "Bob Eberle for Congress 7th District", 6477.PM0175; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Eberle, Bob
  - Farmer Campaign, 1968; 6477.PM0176; Items: 2 (Box 28)
  - "For the Record", 6477.PM0177; Items: 3 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Fish Jr., Ham
  - "An Evening with Gerald Ford...", August 26, 1968; 6477.PM0178; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Ford, Gerald Party: Republican
  - "A Time of Challenge and Crisis", 1968; 6477.PM0179; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Foreman, Ed Party: Republican
  - "Garry for Justice", 6477.PM0180; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Garry, Elizabeth
  - "Elect Francis A Gencarelli", 6477.PM0181; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Gencarelli, Francis
  - Anti Tom Golisano handouts, 6477.PM0182; Items: 4 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Golisano, Tom
  - "For Congressman Mason Hampton", 6477.PM0183; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Hampton, Mason
  - "People and Progress...Stewart F. Hancock", 6477.PM0184; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Hancock, Stewart F. Jr.
  - "Meet Orval Hansen", 6477.PM0185; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Hansen, Orval
  - "Ray Harris for Congress", 6477.PM0186; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Harris, Ray
  - Maurice Hinchey handouts, 1992; 6477.PM0187; Items: 2 (Box 28)
  - President Hoover material, 1930, 1932; 6477.PM0188; Items: 2 (Box 28)
  - "Massachusetts Redistricting of Congressional Districts", 1967; 6477.PM0189; Items: 1 (Box 28)
  - "Our Government is only as good as the People we Elect", 1992; 6477.PM0190; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Houghton, Amo
  - "A Recipe for good Government is a vote for Herb Howell for Congress", 6477.PM0191; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Howell, Herb
  - "Try a New View. Elect Tom Ireland to Congress", 6477.PM0192; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Ireland, Tom
  - "Community Meeting Notice from Randy Kuhl", 2002; 6477.PM0193; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Kuhl, Randy
  - "Elect the Man in Congress who will Win in November", 6477.PM0194; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Landgraf, Vernon
  - "Mike Lane for Assembly", 6477.PM0195; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Lane, Mike
  - "Congressman Gary Lee", 1982; 6477.PM0196; Items: 1 (Box 28)
  - Lew Lehrman mailers, 6477.PM0197; Items: 3 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Lehrman, Lew
  - Lifton fliers, 6477.PM0198; Items: 8 (Box 28)
  - "You Ought to Vote for Joe Lovingood", 6477.PM0199; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Lovingood, Joe Z.
  - "Let's Get Tough: Manuel Lujan, Jr., 6477.PM0200; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Lujan, Jr, Manuel
  - Macneil mailers, 6477.PM0201; Items: 3 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Macneil, Sam
  - "Letter of the Hon. Dudley Marvin of New York", 1848; 6477.PM0202; Items: 2 (Box 28)
  - Bill Mather mailers, 6477.PM0203; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Matherm, Bill
  - "Tompkins County Vote Row B", 6477.PM0204; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: McCall-Mehiel
  - McHugh mailers, 1982; 6477.PM0205; Items: 4 (Box 28)
    Candidate: McHugh, Matt
  - "Maryland Needs McKnight", 1968; 6477.PM0206; Items: 3 (Box 28)
    Candidate: McKnight, Mike
  - "Elect Joe McQuade", 6477.PM0207; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: McQuade, Joe
  - "Elect Mercogliano Congressman", 6477.PM0208; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Mercogliano, Louis
  - Meskill mailers, 6477.PM0209; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Meskill, Peter
  - Howard Miller, 1968; 6477.PM0210; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Miller Jr, Howard
  - "Republican on the Move!", 6477.PM0211; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Mills, Louis V.
  - "Young Man-of-Action...", 6477.PM0212; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Murray, Richard D.
  - "Elect Pete Myers", 6477.PM0213; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Myers, Pete
  - Nickell mailers, 6477.PM0214; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Nickell, Jim
  - Nixon related newspaper, copies of photograph, 1968; 6477.PM0215; Items: 6 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Nixon, Richard
  - Michelle Obama reception invitation, 2007; 6477.PM0216; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Obama, Michelle
  - "What Will it Take", 6477.PM0217; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Odell, Mike
    Party:Republican
  - "Bill Osteen for Congress", 6477.PM0218; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Osteen, Bill
  - Pataki absentee ballot application, 6477.PM0219; Items: 1 (Box 28)
  - "Work and Vote for Mike Posey", 6477.PM0220; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Posey, Mike
  - Reagan magazine clippings, 6477.PM0221; Items: 4 (Box 28)
  - "Donald Riegle Announcement of Candidacy for the US Congress", 1966; 6477.PM0222; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Riegle, Donald
    Election: 1966
  - "Vote for Gilbert A. Robinson", 1962; 6477.PM0223; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Robinson, Gilbert
  - "Elect Rust US Congress", 1967; 6477.PM0224; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Rust, Robert
  - "Earl Ruth for Congress", 6477.PM0225; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Ruth, Earl
  - "Civic Dinner honoring councilman Mike Schaefer", 6477.PM0226; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Schaefer, Mike
  - "A Personal Note to Tompkins County Republicans...", 6477.PM0227; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Seward, Jim
  - "Shute--this is News Worthy", "Denny Shute speaks for Maine", 1968; 6477.PM0228; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Shute, Denny
  - Sigler mailers, 6477.PM0229; Items: 3 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Sigler, Mike
  - "For America's sake a New Team", 6477.PM0230; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Smith, Bob
  - "Legislative Report from Senator William Smith", 6477.PM0231; Items: 2 (Box 28)
  - Souter handouts, 6477.PM0232; Items: 6 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Souter, Sydney
  - "Spitzer Paterson day one, everything changes, 6477.PM0233; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Spitzer and Paterson
  - "Fred Steele Will Represent You", 6477.PM0234; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Steele, Fred
  - "Elect Strauss", 6477.PM0235; Items: 3 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Strauss, Ronald
  - "Vote for Florence Sullivan", 6477.PM0236; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Sullivan, Florence
  - "Tom Sweeney for Congress", 6477.PM0237; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Sweeney, Tom
  - Thompson papers, 6477.PM0238; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Thompson, Fletcher
  - "Congress Needs Mike Thompson", 6477.PM0239; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Thompson, Mike
  - "Elect Everett Thoren to Congress", 1964; 6477.PM0240; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Thoren, Everett
  - "The Van Buren Platform", 6477.PM0241; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Van Buren, Martin
  - "Inaugural Adress of John Volpe", 1967; 6477.PM0242; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Volpe, John
  - "George Wallace and Reece Gardner Share the Same Ideas", 1964; 6477.PM0243; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Wallace, George and Reece Gardner
  - Weeden pamphlet, 6477.PM0244; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Weeden, Don
  - "Weicker for Congress", 6477.PM0245; Items: 1 (Box 28)
  - "Whitehurst for Congress", 6477.PM0246; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Whitehurst, G. William
  - "Wysinger for Congress Committee", 1968; 6477.PM0247; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Wysinger,
  - Communist handout, 6477.PM0248; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Party: Communist
  - "Abbott is Running", 6477.PM0249; Items: 3 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Abbott, Bill
  - "A Report from your Congressman", 1965; 6477.PM0250; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Curtis, Tom
  - Dunn mailers, 1968; 6477.PM0251; Items: 5 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Dunn, James
  - Fargher mailers, 6477.PM0252; Items: 4 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Fargher, Larry
  - Ray Gabler mailers, 1968; 6477.PM0253; Items: 5 (Box 27)
  - "Vote Roger Ladd for Congress!", 1968; 6477.PM0254; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - "Congressman Joe Resnick Reports", 1968; 6477.PM0255; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Resnick, Joe
  - Warren Position papers, 2 photographs, 1968; 6477.PM0256; Items: 7 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Warrern, Douglas
  - Democratic voter guide, 6477.PM0257; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - Presidential Electoral Vote, 1892-1942 card, 6477.PM0258; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - Miscellaneous sales sheets, 6477.PM0259; Items: 4 (Box 28)
  - John Curtis Wood photograph, 6477.PM0260; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Wood, John Curtis
  - "This is John T Williams", 6477.PM0261; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Williams, John
  - Unidentified candidates photographs, multiple copies, 6477.PM0262; Items: 2 (Box 28)
  - "Republican Nomination", 1815; 6477.PM0263; Items: 2 (Box 28)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson inauguration invitation, 1815; 6477.PM0264; Items: 1 (Box 28)
  - Clinton/Perot/Bush issues chart, ca. 1992; 6477.PM0265; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate:Bill Clinton, George Bush, Ross Perot
    Party: Democratic/Republican/Independent
  - "Perot '92 - Florida, United We Stand - America" newsletter, 1992; 6477.PM0266; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Ross Perot
  - $70 bills from Andrew Tobius' birthday, Undated; 6477.PM0267; Items: 1 (Box 28)
  - W. J. Shatas Advertising materials, 1951-1964; No ID; Items: 10 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Various Republican including Eisenhower, Dwight D.
    Election: Various
    Includes items for Big Elephant club, Republican Supply Co, correspondence to campaign managers, button and pin price lists.
  - News About Pres Bush for U.S. Senate letterhead, 1951-1964; No ID; Items: 1 (Box 28)
    Election: 1952 or 1956
- Series X. Parades
  - LBJ For The USA Clear Plastic Banner, ca. 1964; 6477.PD0001; Items: 1 (Box 18)
- Series XI. Posters
  - Get It On!: Join the Republican Party!, 1971; 6477.PO0001; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Reagan Takes Oath as 40th President, 1981; 6477.PO0002; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Agnew for Vice President, ca. 1968-1972; 6477.PO0003; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
    Election: 1968, 1972
  - Richard Nixon: President of the United States, ca. 1969-1974; 6477.PO0004; Items: 2 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Richard M. Nixon Portrait, ca. 1968-1974; 6477.PO0005; Items: 2 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Perfectly Clear, ca. 1968-1972; 6477.PO0006; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Take the Bugs Out of Government: Vote McGovern, ca. 1972; 6477.PO0007; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - I want America to come home ..., 1972; 6477.PO0008; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - This Time, Vote Like Alice Simms' Whole World Depended On It., ca. 1968-1972; 6477.PO0009; Items: 2 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - This Time, Vote Like Homer Pitts' Whole World Depended On It., ca. 1968-1972; 6477.PO0010; Items: 3 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - The President for Precedent, 1972; 6477.PO0011; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Nixon and Agnew as Convicts, 1973; 6477.PO0012; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - McGovern-Shriver '72 (blue), ca. 1972; 6477.PO0013; Items: 2 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - McGovern-Shriver '72 (black and white), ca. 1972; 6477.PO0014; Items: 6 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - For Peace and Honesty: McGovern for President, ca. 1972; 6477.PO0015; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - McGovern President '72, 1972; 6477.PO0016; Items: 9 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - A Time to Grow in a World of Permanent Change: Vote McGovern President, ca. 1972; 6477.PO0017; Items: 2 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - McGovern: Let the Sun Shine In, ca. 1972; 6477.PO0018; Items: 2 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - McGovern: Work / Vote, ca. 1972; 6477.PO0019; Items: 2 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - McGovern for President, ca. 1972; 6477.PO0020; Items: 2 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - McGovern: " ... We Can Help to Change the Future", ca. 1972; 6477.PO0021; Items: 3 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Republican Elephant, ca. 1960-1980; 6477.PO0022; Items: 2 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Performing Under Pressure: Athletes for the President, ca. 1972; 6477.PO0023; Items: 4 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Now More Than Ever, ca. 1972; 6477.PO0024; Items: 2 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Re-Elect the President, ca. 1972; 6477.PO0025; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Roosevelt and Johnson, 1912; 6477.PO0026; Items: 1 (Box Conservation Lab)
  - Governor Rockefeller: He's Done a Lot. He'll Do More., ca. 1966-1970; 6477.PO0027; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
    Election: 1966, 1970
  - Re-elect Attorney General Louis J. Lefkowitz "The People's Lawyer", ca. 1966-1970; 6477.PO0028; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Join the March for America: James L. Buckley for Senator, ca. 1968-1976; 6477.PO0029; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
    Election: 1968, 1970, 1976
  - Keep Senator Goodell He's Too Good to Lose., ca. 1970; 6477.PO0030; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Goldberg / Patterson, ca. 1970; 6477.PO0031; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Ottinger for Senator, ca. 1970; 6477.PO0032; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Duryea. Caputo. A New Team for New York., ca. 1978; 6477.PO0033; Items: 2 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
    Candidate: Duryea, Perry B.
  - Justice Bernard S. Meyer, ca. 1978; 6477.PO0034; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
    Candidate: Meyer, Bernard S.
  - He's Making Us Proud Again, ca. 1976; 6477.PO0035; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Roosevelt and Johnson Mass Meeting Poster, ca. 1912; 6477.PO0036; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
  - William McKinley Portrait, 1900; 6477.PO0037; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
    Candidate: McKinley, William, Jr.
  - Theodore Roosevelt Portrait, 1900; 6477.PO0038; Items: 2 (Box n/a)
  - Nixon: Giant Fold-Out Environmental Poster, ca. 1972; 6477.PO0039; Items: 2 (Box 19)
  - "Romney Home Headquarters" Poster, ca. 1968; 6477.PO0040; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
  - "The American Presidency" (From Washington thru Nixon), ca. 1789-1972; 6477.PO0041; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
  - Johnson Humphrey For The USA Poster (28-1/2" x 20-1/4"), 1964; 6477.PO0042; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
  - Johnson Humphrey For The USA Poster (20-1/4" x 13"), 1964; 6477.PO0043; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
  - Let's Put Bob Kennedy To Work For New York, 1964; 6477.PO0044; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
  - Re-Elect Connie Cook Republican For Assembly Poster, 1964; 6477.PO0045; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
  - Vote Goldwater President Poster, 1964; 6477.PO0046; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
  - Goldwater For President Posters, 1964; 6477.PO0047; Items: 2 (Box n/a)
  - Miller For Vice President Posters, 1964; 6477.PO0048; Items: 2 (Box n/a)
  - New York's Own! Keep Keating Your U.S. Senator Posters, 1964; 6477.PO0049; Items: 2 (Box n/a)
  - The Perils Of Poverty And Perle's Back In Town! (Home-made Poster: Anti-LBJ?), ca. 1964; 6477.PO0050; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
  - My Goodness I'm Not Voting Democratic...(Home-made Poster with Cat picture), ca. 1964; 6477.PO0051; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
  - Senator From N.Y.? (Home-made Poster: Anti-Robert Kennedy), 1964; 6477.PO0052; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
  - Helen Amdur Candidate For Tompkins County Judge, ca. 1970; 6477.PO0053; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
    Candidate: Amdur, Helen
  - Johnson Humphrey For The U S A, 1964; 6477.PO0054; Items: 1 (Box n/a)
  - Benjamin Harrison (Portrait with facsimile signature), 1888; 6477.PO0055; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Levi P. Morton (Portrait with facsimile signature), 1888; 6477.PO0056; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
    Candidate: Morton, Levi P.
  - Warner Miller (Portrait with facsimile signature), 1888; 6477.PO0057; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
    Candidate: Miller, Warner
  - William McKinley...Garret A. Hobart..., 1896; 6477.PO0058; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Garret A. Hobart Republican Candidate For Vice President, 1896; 6477.PO0059; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
    Candidate: Hobart, Garret A.
  - William McKinley Republican Candidate For President, 1896; 6477.PO0060; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - For President Alton B. Parker...Vice President Henry G. Davis..., 1904; 6477.PO0061; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
    Candidate: Parker, Alton B.
  - For Governor D. Cady Herrick...Lieut. Governor Francis Burton Harrison, 1904; 6477.PO0062; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
    Candidate: Herrick, D. Cady
  - For Governor Frank W. Higgins...Lieut. Governor M. Linn Bruce, 1904; 6477.PO0063; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
    Candidate: Higgins, Frank W.
  - Theodore Roosevelt, 1904; 6477.PO0064; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Charles W. Fairbanks, 1904; 6477.PO0065; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - McKinley-Hobart Flag Day Poster, 1896; 6477.PO0066; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Souvenir Of The Return Of James G. Blaine August 1888, 1888; 6477.PO0067; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
    Candidate: Blaine, James G.
  - How Protected Manufacturers Favor Foreigners, ca. 1890; 6477.PO0068; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - James Farmer, 6477.PO0069; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Truman, Eisenhower, Roosevelt, Nixon, Johnson, 6477.PO0070; Items: 5 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
- Series XII. Prints
  - Nixon Portrait Bust, ca. 1960-1974; 6477.PR0001; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson: Thirty-Sixth President of the United States, 1963; 6477.PR0002; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Gore-Lieberman Group Portraits, ca. 2002; 6477.PR0003; Items: 3 (Box 19)
  - Samuel Seabury Candidate For Governor Of New York State, ca. 1916; 6477.PR0004; Items: 2 (Box 17)
  - Doug Auer Standing Next To Gary Lee Billboard (Photograph), ca. 1976; 6477.PR0005; Items: 1 (Box 19)
  - Walter Mondale And Geraldine Ferrero (Photograph), ca. 1984; 6477.PR0006; Items: 2 (Box 19)
  - Bill And Hillary Rodham Clinton ("Thank You" Photograph), 1994; 6477.PR0007; Items: 1 (Box 19)
    Candidate: Clinton, William F.
  - Bill Clinton In Front Of Flag (Photograph), ca. 1992;1996; 6477.PR0008; Items: 1 (Box 19)
    Election: 1992;1996
  - Bill Clinton And Thomas S. Foley (Photograph), ca; 1992; 1996; 6477.PR0009; Items: 1 (Box 19)
- Series XIII. Ribbons
  - Grant and Colfax White Crossstich Ribbon, ca. 1868; 6477.RB0001; Items: 1 (Box 17)
    Candidate: Grant, Ulysses S.
    Election: 1868
  - "Committee Bryan Reception Madison Square Garden New York City Oct. 10, 1900" Ribbon Fragment, 1900; 6477.RB0002; Items: 1 (Box 14)
    Candidate: Bryan, William Jennings
  - The Progressive Party Founders' Day (Paper Ribbon), 1912; 6477.RB0003; Items: 1 (Box 14)
  - Republican National Convention Phila.1940: Ribbon w. Button & Dangling Plastic Elephant, 1940; 6477.RB0004; Items: 1 (Box 14)
  - Badge: "Assistant Sergeant-At-Arms Ohio Republican State Convention", 1908; 6477.RB0005; Items: 1 (Box 14)
  - "GOP Truth Squad" Badge., n/a; 6477.RB0006; Items: 1 (Box 14)
  - "GOP Truth Squad" Badge., n/a; 6477.RB0007; Items: 1 (Box 14)
  - Housewives For Rocky (Ribbon/Banner), ca. 1970; 6477.RB0008; Items: 1 (Box 17)
- Series XIV. Scrapbooks
  - Political Campaign Of 1888 (And Other Years), 6477.SY0001; Items: 1 (Box 15)
  - Democratic Party Campaign Leaflets, 1900; 6477.SY0002; Items: 1 (Box 15)
- Series XV. Sheet Music
  - Look Ahead, Neighbor!, 1952; 6477.SM0001; Items: 1 (Box 19)
  - Ike For Four More Years, 1956; 6477.SM0002; Items: 1 (Box 19)
- Series XVI. Songbooks
  - Republican Campaign Songbook 1880, 1880; 6477.SB0001; Items: 1 (Box 19)
    Candidate: Garfield, James A.
    Election: 1880
  - Republican Campaign Songbooks, 1880s; 6477.SB0002; Items: 5 (Box 28)
- Series XVII. Textiles
  - Republican Elephant Scarf, ca. 1968-2000; 6477.TX0001; Items: 1 (Box 18)
  - Eisenhower Toile, ca. 1956; 6477.TX0002; Items: 1 (Box 18)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Handkerchief, ca. 1912; 6477.TX0003; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Bandana, ca. 1904-1912; 6477.TX0004; Items: 1 (Box 18)
    Election: 1904; 1912
    Party: Republican; Progressive
  - Taft-Sherman Silk Handkerchief, 1909; 6477.TX0005; Items: 1 (Box 17)
    Candidate: Taft, William
  - Crazy Quilt Embroidered "McKinley 1900", 1900; 6477.TX0006; Items: 1 (Box 16)
- Series XVIII. Trinkets
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Inaugural Medal, Case and Stand, 1957; 6477.TK0001; Items: 3 (Box 13)
  - Small Cloth Badge: Laurel Wreath with US in center, n/a; 6477.TK0002; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - Republican Elephant Holding Flag in His Trunk (Broken), n/a; 6477.TK0003; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - G.O.P. Elephant Nametag: William E. Miller Chairman, ca.1961-1964; 6477.TK0004; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - G.O.P. Elephant Nametag: William E. Miller Chairman, ca.1961-1964; 6477.TK0005; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - Wooden Elephant Pin, ca. 1940; 6477.TK0006; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - G.O.P. Elephant Nametag, ca. 1964; 6477.TK0007; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - 1968, 6477.TK0008"Wallace '68" Gold Pin; Items: 1 (Box 13)
  - Silver Elephant Pins "'52", ca. 1952; 6477.TK0009; Items: 15 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pins "'52", ca. 1952; 6477.TK0010; Items: 3 (Box 12)
  - Gold Elephant Pin "'52", ca. 1952; 6477.TK0011; Items: 1 (Box 12)
  - Copper Elephant Pins "'52 G.O.P.", ca. 1952; 6477.TK0012; Items: 23 (Box 12)
  - Copper Elephant Pins "'52 Conn.", ca. 1952; 6477.TK0013; Items: 3 (Box 12)